纽约城的周六晚
年轻的城里人都纷纷出门...
体验纽约才有的疯狂生活方式
100!
100次? 我们度蜜月时才82次
Robin? 我想介绍个男人给你
他很可爱 风趣 很聪明
他的"但是"(缺点)呢?
你什么意思?
有人想为你介绍朋友时
总会先告诉你对方的优点
但他们故意不提对方的严重缺陷
她绝对性感 绝对幽默
但是她有颗坏牙
她性感无比 还事业有成
但是她喜欢把哈巴狗放婴儿车里
到处推着跑
她太可爱了 极其聪明
但是她最近一任男友不得不
把她关在家里
接着他的猫和真空吸尘器就不翼而飞了
哇 介绍给我!
我仍然确信她杀死了我的海龟
嘿 知道不?
不是所有的相亲都有个"但是"
那个...Jamie 怎么说?
Lily介绍给你的?
- 对哦
- 她人真的很好
如果我没记错的话 她有大大的"但是"
她的屁股太大了
("但是"和"屁股"在英文里谐音)
- 一语中的!
- 对哦
这家伙毫无缺点
他真是个好人 真的很可爱
- 但是?
- 好吧
但是他有个孩子
就是说嘛!
Robin不会和有孩子的男人出去
但他真的很出色 他孩子也很可爱
他在我的班上
那不重要 Robin痛恨孩子
我不恨孩子
你告诉我 说你还是孩子时就恨孩子了
Robin 你能和我一起看卡通片吗?
我整个礼拜都要上学
我就不能留5分钟给自己
看看报纸大标题 喝点橙汁吗?
好吧  孩子不是我最喜欢的
但我喜欢他们
你不想要孩子
我喜欢跑车 但这不代表我就想
自己生一辆法拉利出来
这我早说过了
你不能因为我们把孩子看做麻烦
就责怪我们
如果我们是加菲猫的朋友
就不会安排它和星期一去相亲
很好
你们知道不? 孩子不是问题
我要去见见这家伙
- 很好 真酷
- 是啊
那我的"但是"呢? 我是个...
我真得很不错 但是...
但是她害怕承诺
但是她爱枪成痴
但是她是加拿大人
但是她不爱看《梦幻之地》(电影名)
- 我想不出...
- 你没有"但是"
翻译: SharonTang 雨池
好吧  我搞到手了
Here. Put on this eye patch.
给 戴上这眼罩
Why?
干嘛?
终极破冰人
一群眼镜蛇游走在中央公园
你和我正在慢跑...
为成为死亡峡谷的钢铁超人受训
没啥大不了的
我们每年都要训练
突然 我们看到这些该死的小蛇
正游向一个小婴儿
虽然我们并不当班
你抓住孩子 我空手扼死六条响尾蛇
纽约的女士们 一次上一位 拜托大家了
那么眼罩是怎么回事?
我们被蛇咬了
- 咬在眼睛上了?
- 对
两个都咬了?
咬到不同的眼睛了
我看不出这怎么惹着你了
戴上眼罩!
Robin去和George约会了
那家伙有一个孩子 后来...
好吧 这就是问题所在
George是个好男人 我们玩得很高兴
但是?
太好了 我等不及见到他
等不及见到他?
我干嘛要说那句话?
我不想见他的孩子
你知道 你早晚得见他
我只想以后见他 比如再过20年
我是钓小帅哥的老妇 他长到他爸那样性感
Rboin 那有什么关系?
他只是个孩子 他不会咬你
也许他会咬人
我们正教育他们不要咬人
为什么孩子会在她身边?
他不该和妈妈在一起吗?
什么样的律师能整天照顾孩子?
好的律师 他赢得了监护权
他赢得了? 是他赢到的?
上帝 得到孩子就是获胜 是不是?
- 别告诉别人我这样说
- 当然了
我出去买了眼罩
你打算怎么做赢得美眉芳心?
好吧 我要告诉你点小秘密
真正的游戏中 玩家不需要眼罩
瞧这德行
不 不 不
没有我 你都不知道游戏怎么玩
我是最棒的游戏高手
我玩过太多游戏了
我是Cornish游戏鸡(即童子鸡)
是吗? 我是纽约州游戏专员
那我就是游戏了
制作精湛 悬念引人 卡司强大
Michael Douglas和Sean Penn领衔主演
你们在这里 没去厕所啊
对 怎么了?
我也许和某个穿的鞋与你们相同的人
发表了番关于同志的不恰当言论
- 好吧 Marshall?
- 我在
我们俩谁赢的游戏多?
你们谁都没赢过 行了吧?
否则你们就象我这样 结婚了
什么?
如果约会是游戏 结婚就是游戏获胜
没错 如果你玩的是女人游戏
你开玩笑 我的游戏玩得棒极了 兄弟
行了 第一: 我们赞同不再说"兄弟"
这周不错 我们玩得很高兴 但结束了
第二: 你和Lily在一起有11年了
你对好游戏的想法就是
戴上苏斯博士(儿童文学作家)的帽子
亮出两张Spin Doctor的音乐会门票
(90年代初的摇滚乐队名)
我不想这么说 但你有点过时了
什么? 我可没过时
我有很多点子 我能帮到你们
我不想被排除在外
Ted 你玩过的游戏不比我多
仅仅在Sheerbers 我就赢你了
得了 朋友 你看过我的征服者名单
你们想听听我的故事吗?
首先 我居然没被邀请看那份名单
我仍感到惊诧莫名
真正的游戏在乎质量 而不是数量
任何时候 上档次的女孩总喜欢选我
而不是你
你是模特吗?
说得真动听 是句恭维话
对女孩来说
- Ted 我向你挑战 进行一次钓美眉奥运会
- 没问题
在11周内 展开26项竞赛
我们将去一个中立城市
由一个国际裁判团...
或者我们只挑一个女孩
看谁先勾上手 谁就是赢家?
那也不错
就她 怎么样?
同意
我们开始前 干嘛不确定基本规则呢?
很好 不许戴眼罩 或任何其他道具...
有一次 我碰到某个女孩
我试了你那个模特的说法
我隔着衣服看到她的胸部激突了
伙计 别说了 你唠唠叨叨
快把人都赶跑了
规则二-- 赌注为100万美元
- 我赢了
- 怎么赢的?
我和她睡过 大概一年前
我刚才忘记了
那不算数
赌约从我们握手那刻开始
但我不能再和她睡了 她恨我
有意思 看看现在谁大幅领先了
没你干扰 我就能享受甜蜜时光了
Ted 她就要走了
别挡着道
根据那鞋子的式样 你的厕所朋友来了
看看谁赢了比赛
那么说 你是个喜欢孩子的人 哈?
我最最喜欢孩子了
我觉得孩子太伟大了 特别是 小娃娃
你知道的...小胖墩 还坐不起来
牙齿都没长出来时
- 牙牙学语的婴儿?
- 对 我就喜欢那样的
Doug差不多要6岁了 所以...
哦 6岁太棒了
你会喜欢6岁孩子的
6岁就是当他们真正开始 呃...
我讨厌孩子
抱歉 你说什么?
我是说 我不恨孩子
我- 我只是不喜欢孩子
我是说 对 他们的鞋子真是小得可爱
但除此以外 还有什么吸引人的?
- 你一定觉得我是个怪人
- 什么? 不 不 不
我...那么说你不喜欢孩子 那又怎样?
我没在为Doug找母亲
我们干嘛不推迟见他的时间呢?
是啊 慢慢来
孩子 那正是她要面对的
于是 在另一天--绝不是次天清晨
Robin不得不面对她最恐惧的场面
嘿 什么事?
它就在这里 Lily
它正朝我看
那个孩子 我该怎么办?
只要和他聊聊就好 你能做到的 Robin
你是谁?
我是Robin
那是鸟的名字
(Robin有知更鸟的意思)
不 不是 事实上 它只是鸟的一个种类
我朋友Patrick有只长尾小鹦鹉就叫Robin
所以这么说
你想用摩尔斯电码来说话吗?
朋友 我是- 我只是在看报纸 所以...
我饿死了 你能为我做麦片吗?
当然可以
你在干什么? 你该先倒牛奶的
什么? 不 你该先倒麦片
这样你就知道该放多少牛奶了
先放牛奶 味道更好!
一旦倒进碗里 尝起来就是一个味了
你干嘛穿我爸爸的裤子?
那就先放牛奶吧
你在看什么?
商业版
美联储将降低利率以刺激次优抵押贷款
一堆傻瓜
Aldrin小姐说骂人不好
如果他们不是傻瓜 我就不会那样叫他们
我当时也这么说
你真酷
你也是
与此同时 Stacey和我开始约会
Stacey就是酒吧里那女孩
无论如何 我快要成功时
意想不到的事发生了
我开始喜欢上她了
瑜珈课开心
她正在增强她的核心力量
我觉得那会很棒
是吗? 好的
过一会见 鳄鱼
看到这个了吗?
游戏大王
随你说吧 Ted
看看这个
她在一个雷吉乐队当贝司手
他们周五有场演出
很了不起吧?
她知道那首歌吗?
Mm-mm,chaka,mm-mm,chaka
这歌叫什么名来着?
对了 它就叫"每一首雷吉歌"
- 我没跑题
- 什么?
我算过数字了
如果我和Lily每周2次作爱 坦率说
我们都知道这数字太保守了
我们在一起10年了 加上蜜月时17次多
减去2周无性生活 因为我说杂货店的店员
很象年轻时的Lily
- 这样我们的作爱次数总共--等等
- 不错
1053又二分之一次
那半次是我妈打电话来
但比Barney的总做爱次数多多了
根据你的观点 Ted,
Lily是个上档次的女孩
我赢了
法定胜利
不算数
- 当然算数
- 你是对的
它算数 只能算一次
你只有过一次性约会 怎么样?
我还是不错
好吧 Ted 去赢下赌注吧
我祝福你 她是个好姑娘
我该知道的
好的
好吧 我知道你打什么主意
我们从来没分享过女人 对吗 Ted?
那不是很有意思吗?
现在是你和她在一起
一年前 我和她在一起
你自己算算 对她来说
就是洗200次淋浴之前的事
你扪心自问一下 洗200次够了吗?
知道不?
我才不介意呢
是啊 你当然不介意了
就象第二个爬上珠穆朗玛峰的人
历经千辛万苦攀上顶峰...
只发现Edmund Hillary爵士的旗杆
深深地插入柔软顺从的顶峰
不 我确定你和她在一起时
你才不会想到我呢
亲吻我早已亲吻过的地方
爱抚我早已爱抚过的地方 做...
做我早就做过的事
- Barney 我不怕抓你留下的虱子 好吧?
- 真的吗?
- Ted 不怕虱子?
- 当然了
好吧 我想你也不介意尝一口
我的琴酒加汤力水了?
没问题
我只用小拇指搅过它
猜猜谁才是爱Robin的人
孩子 孩子热爱Robin
Doug认为我很酷
真的 那太好了!
你和George 都是我牵线搭桥
对 我打算和他分手
什么?
就是...
和孩子的事有点过于认真了
这不是我想寻求的生活
所以现在分手 比他粘得更紧时分手要好
什么?
我讨厌告诉你这个 但是...太晚了
"我的新妈妈" 今天上课时他画的
哦 见鬼
这幅画不可能是我
那个女人戴着圆环型耳环
我甚至都没有圆环型耳环
我有过一副 是金耳环 那些是水果环
你在抗拒现实 你做的就象
你在感情关系里做的那样
一旦你接近某个男人 你就想退出
好吧 正式说法 他才6岁
但这观点仍然成立
好吧  我们去问问男人们
他们会告诉你 她不是我
那绝对是你
你... 你们简直是胡说
嘿 这是谁画的robin?
这不是我
你在开玩笑吧?
这不是我!
我是新妈妈
好像有个漂亮的戒指蕴含其中
嘿 如果你当妈妈的话 你会不会开始
穿裤腰一直到胸部的牛仔裤?
你们真的觉得这是我吗?
宝贝 这就是你啊
如果你想和george分手的话
你也必须要和他的孩子分手
真的吗?
是啊 你不能就这么把他扔在一边
你得亲口和他说
来吧 robin
你也知道这么做才是对的
噢 天哪
Doug说的对: 你真是个难缠的主儿
今晚我真的很高兴
- 我也是
- 是吗?
嘿 Ted 再怎么生气也没用
我已经先你一步了
从这里出发
我也已经探索过下面的两座大山了
ted?
怎么了?
嘿 doug
你是来见我爸爸的吗?
他正在洗澡
实际上 我是来见你的
我写了首诗 你想听听吗?
当然了 怎么能不听呢?
致我的新妈妈
你很漂亮
你很善良
你的味道就像菊花
哇 真是太好了
尽管一点都不押韵
听着 嗯 doug
说这些话一直都很难 嗯...
Robin阿姨不知道该说些什么
从来没有人甩过这些孩子
于是她意识到...
她可以用书上的那些酸词了
我们得谈谈了
我只是觉得 我们都需要一些空间
问题不在你 问题在我
我知道这听起来很难过
但你应该拥有个更好的女人
我现在只是想把重心放到事业上
你明白吗?
我只是希望我们还能继续做朋友
我叫Brooke 我是来和george约会的
你一定就是那个保姆了
我刚才喝太多咖啡了
我得赶紧去趟洗手间 你好啊 dougie
这是怎么一回事?
那是我的新妈妈
这么说...
这上面画的不是我了?
我为什么要画你?
她和你爸爸约会过几次?
两次
我差不多和你爸约会过五次了
但你却更喜欢她?
我们之间真的很有感觉
那和我呢?
你觉得我就是为城里的每个
孩子冲麦片的吗?
你干吗这么生气啊 roberta?
Robin 我叫robin
和小鸟的名字一样 还记得吗?
好吧好吧
这么说结束了 是吧?
- 听着 你人很好 但是...
- 好吧
总会有但是
嗯 我做不到
我和她分手了
顺便说一下 这都要感谢你
一个漂亮的性感女孩
但我想的却都是你已经捷足先登了
你就像一首瑞格舞曲
一样萦绕在我的脑袋里
哪首瑞格舞曲?
哇 看来事情有了奇妙的转机了
看起来似乎我要获胜了
你怎么能说获胜?
你连和她说话都做不到
上次你去搭讪结果被扇了一巴掌
那是你认为的情况
嗯 好极了
规则一: 不许用眼罩或是别的小道具...
事情是这样: 我朋友刚被人甩了
所以他现在有点腼腆
但他很想请你喝上一杯
然后认识认识你
但问题是 他觉得像你这样的漂亮女生
是不会看上他那样的人的
所以你能不能扇我一巴掌
让他相信你不喜欢那种油嘴滑舌的人?
你看怎样? 就当是为了我的朋友?
你真是太好了
所以 无论Ted对她表现的多好
在她的印象里
我就是那个比他还要好的人
那你没和她上过床了?
绝对没有
哇 这招赞
实际上还要更好
还记得Ted和她打的那次电话吗?
好吧 好好享受瑜伽吧
嗯...
- 我...
- 对不起
- Stacey 没记错吧?
- 没错...
- 噢 你是那天酒吧里面Ted的朋友 对吧?
- 是啊
- 等等 别告我说你也在这里练瑜伽
- 我是在这里练啊
她在瑞格乐队里面担任贝斯手
接下来我准备去听场瑞格音乐会
- 我是瑞格音乐的狂热粉丝
- 噢 天哪!
- 我就是瑞格乐队的
- 不会吧
那怎么Ted不早告诉我
我说过了 我是瑞格音乐的狂热粉丝
嗯...
那我进去了
一会儿见 小鳄鱼
- 再见 鳄...
- 在家 鳄...
我们真是心有灵犀
哇 那你保重吧
嗯 你好(印度语)
你真是小人
那可是我的瑜伽垫
现在既然Ted已经出局了
我就要来夺取胜利果实了
为什么?
Parce que j'ai le jeu,mes chiennes
翻译过来是: 因为我才是游戏玩家 贱人们
不 不 这什么也说明不了 因为...
等一下
是stacey
嘿 stace?
怎么了呀?
他不会这样吧!
待着别动
我马上就过去
我当初就应该戴着那个破眼罩
噢 真不敢相信你被六岁的孩子甩了
管他呢 他是个傻瓜
我是... 我是再也不想接触小孩了
当然了 robin最后还是喜欢上了小孩子
你们也知道 她在很多人的作品中
都出现过 尤其是你们的作品
我们和ROBIN阿姨
我们和ROBIN阿姨去动物园
我们和ROBIN阿姨去海滩
一个月之后
嘿
知道吗 我真的很感谢你
同意让我们的关系慢慢发展
自从ted之后 你也知道 我...
我实在不想太快的有身体关系
你就是这样特别 宝贝
不管了 一想到明天就要
演奏"光斑" 我就很激动
我们大概要从11:00演到6:00
所以保险起见你最好9:00前就到场
噢 那里会有不少泥巴的
It was saturday night in new york city,
and the young metropolitan
set was out on the town,
living the kind of crazy lifestyle
you can only find in the big apple.
100!
A hundred? We only got
to 82 on our honeymoon.
So,robin? I've got a guy for you.
He's cute. He's funny.He's smart.
What's his but?
What do you mean?
When someone wants to set you up,they
always tell you their good qualities first,
but then they leave out their huge flaw.
She's totally hot and really fun.
Barney: But she has a dead tooth.
She's super-hot,and
she's so successful.
But she has a pug that she
pushes around in a stroller.
She's so cute,and she's so smart.
But her last boyfriend had to get
a restraining order against her,
and then his cat and new
vacuum cleaner both went missG.
Set it up!
I'm still convinced
she killed my turtle.
Hey,you know what? Not
every setup has a but.
What about,um,jamie,that girl
that lily set you up with?
- Yeah.
- She was really nice.
If memory serves me,she had a huge but.
Her huge butt.
- Nailed it!
- Yeah.
Well,there'innoths g
wrong with this guy.
He's really nice,and he's really cute...
- but?
- Fine.
But he has a kid.
There it is!
Robin's not going out
with a guy with a kid.
But the guy is really
great,and his kid's sweet.
He's in my class.
It doesn't matter. Robin hates kids.
I don't hate kids.
You told me even when you
were a kid,you hated kids.
Robin,will you watch cartoons with me?
I go to school all week.
Can't I just have five minutes to myself
to read highlights and drink my juice?
Okay,yes,kids are not my favorite
thing in the world,but I like them.
Well,you don't want to have them.
I like sports cars,but it doesn't mean I
want to push a ferrari through my vagina.
Shotgun.
you can't blame us for thinking
that the kid would be a problem.
I mean,if we were friends with garfield,we
wouldn't set him up on a date with mondays.
nice.
You know what? The kid is not a problem.
I want to meet this guy.
- Okaythat's awesome!
- Yeah.
Hey,what's my but? You know,I'm A...
I'm really nice,but...
But she's afraid of commitment.
But she's a gun nut.
But she's canadian.
But she didn't like field of dreams.
- I can't think of...
- you don't have a but.
Okay. I've got it.
Here. Put on this eye patch.
Why?
The ultimate ice-breaker.
A bunch of cobras got
loose in central park.
You and I are jogging...
training for the death
valley iron man no big deal.
We do it every year.
Suddenly,we see these snake bastards
sneaking towards a little baby.
Not on our watch.
You grab the kid,I strangle
six cobras with my bare hands.
Women of new york,one at a time,please.
So what are the eye patches for?
We got bit.
- On the eye?
- Yes.
Both of us ?
They're different eyes.
I don'owt kn see why this bumps you!
Patch up!
Ted: So robin went on a date with
george,the guy with the kid,and afterwards...
okay,here's the thing.
George is a great guy.
We had a wonderful date.
But?
Great. I can't wait to meet him.
Can't wait to meet him?
Why did I say that?
I don't want to meet his kid.
Well,you knew you'd
meet him sooner or later.
I was just hoping for later,like in 20 years
when I'm a cougar and he's as hot as his dad.
Robin,what's the big deal?
He's just a kid. He's not going to bite.
He may bite. We're working on biting.
Why is this kid around anyway?
Shouldn't he be with his mom?
I mean,what kind of lawyer does this guy have
if he has to take care of the kid all the time?
A good one. He won full custody.
He won? He won?
Oh,god,getting the kid
is winning,isn't it?
- Don't tell anyone I said that.
- No.
I'm going out buying eye patches.
What are you doing to help score chicks?
Okay,I'm going to let
you in on a little secret.
People with real game
don't need eye patches.
Theodore.
No,no,no.
You can't spell game without
me,and me has the best game.
Yeah,well,I got so much
game,I'm cornish game hen.
Oh,yeah? I'm the new york
state gaming commissioner.
Well,I'm the game.
Well-crafted,keep-you-guessing thriller
starring michael douglas and sean penn.
You're heer and not in stall two.
Yeah. So?
I may have made some wildly inappropriate homoerotic
comments to a gentleman wearing your shoes.
- Okay,marshall?
- Yes.
Which one of us has more game?
Neither of you guys has any game,right?
Or else you'd be married like me.
What?
If dating is the game,then
marriage is winning the game.
Yeah. If you're playing
in the women's league.
You're joking. I have mad game,brah.
Okay,one: We agreed not
to ever say brah anymore.
It was a good week,we had
a lot of fun,but it's over.
You've been with lily for 11.Ears y
your idea of good game is
slapping on a dr.Seuss hat
and flashing two tickets
to a spin doctors concert.
Yeah,I hate to say
it,buddy,but,uh,you're kind of irrelevant.
What? I am not irrelevant.
I know tons of stuff.
I can help you guys.
I don't want to be left out.
Ted,you do not have more game than me.
By sheerbers alone,I win.
Come on,dude. You've seen my list.
You guys want to hear one of my lines?
First of all,I did not ask to see
that list,and I am still horrified.
And true game is about
quality,not quantity,
and a quality girl would
pick me over you any day.
Are you a model?
That one's good because it's flattering.
To the girl.
- Ted,I challenge you to a picking up girls olympiad.
- Fine.
There will be 26 events
spread out over 11 weeks.
We will travel to a neutral city where
a panel of international judges...
or we could just choose a girl,and
the first one to seal e deal wins?
That's good,too.
How about her?
You're on.
Before we start,why don't we jot
down a few basic ground rules?
Okay,great. No eye
patches or props of any...
One time,I was with this
girl,and I tried that model line,
and I totally got some over-the-shirt
boob action in the just say no assembly.
Man,just stop. You're
bumming everybody out.
Rule number two-- this bet
is for one million dollars.
- I win.
- How?
Oh,I slept with her. About a year ago.
I just forgot.
Oh,well,that doesn't count.
The bet started the moment we shook.
But I can't sleep with
her again. She hates me.
Interesting. Look who just
took a commanding lead.
Now with you out of the
picture,I can take my swt time.
Ted,she's leaving.
Get out of my way.
By the look of those shoes,here
comes your bathroom buddy.
Look who's got game.
So,you're a big kids person,huh?
Only the biggest ever.
I think kids are so
great,especially,um,the little ones.
You know,uh... pudgy,can't
sit up,don't have teeth yet.
- Yoan babies?
- Yeah,I like that kind.
Well,doug's almost six,so...
oh,six is great.
Oh,you are going to love six.
Six is when they,uh,they
really start to,um...
I hate kids.
Excuse me. What?
I mean,I don't hate kids.
I'm-I'm just not a kiderson.
I mean,yeah,it's cute that
their shoes are real little,
but beyond that,what's the draw?
- You must think I'm nuts.
- What?No,no,no.
I... so you don't like kids,so what?
And I'm not looking
for a mother for doug.
Uh,why don't we just hold
off on you meeting him?
Yeah. Let's take things slow.
Ted: And kids,that's
exactly what she did.
Then,on a totally different day that
was definitely not the next morning,
aunt robin had to face her worst fear.
Hey,what's up?
It's here,lily.
It's looking at me.
The kid. What do I do?
Just talk to him. You can do this,robin.
Who are you?
Um,I'm robin.
That's a bird's name.
Ah,no,it's not. It's
actually a type of bird.
My friend patrick has a
parakeet named robin,so there.
Do you want to talk in morse code?
Dude,I'm-I'm just
reading my paper,so...
I'm starving. Will you make me cereal?
Sure.
What are you doing? You're
supposed to pour the milk first.
What? No,you pour the cereal first
so you know how much milk you need.
It tastes better milk first!
It all tastes the same
once it's in the bowl.
Why are you wearing my dad's pants?
Milk first it is.
What are you reading?
The business section.
The fed's going to lower rates again
to bail out these sub-prime lenders.
Bunch of idiots.
Ms.Aldrin says it's not
nice to call people names.
Well,maybe if they weren't such
idiots,I wouldn't have to call them that.
That's what I said.
You're pretty cool.
You,too.
Meanwhile,stacey and
i had started dating.
Oh,stacey was the girl from the bar.
Anyway,I was close to winning the bet
when something unexpected happened.
I started to really like her.
Well,have fun in yoga.
She's stngthening her core.
I think that's going to be good.
Yeah? All right.
After a while,crocodile.
you see this?
Game face.
Whatever,ted.
Get this.
She plays bass in a reggae band.
They're hing a show this friday.
How cool is that?
Oh,does she know that one song?
Mm-mm,chaka,mm-mm,chaka.
What's that song called?
Oh,right. It's called every reggae song.
- I am not irrelevant.
- What?
I ran the numbers.
If lily and I have sex twice a week,which let's
be honest,we all know is being conservative,
and we've been togethe for ten
years,plus 17 more times on the honeymoon,
minus the two-week drought when I said the checker
at the grocery store reminded me of a young lily,
then we have had sex a total
of-- wait for it-- nice.
1,053-1/2 times.
My mom called once.
But that's more times than
barney has ever had sex,
and to your point,ted,lily
is a quality girl.
I win.
Lawyered.
Doesn't count.
- It totally counts.
- You're right.
It does count. It counts as one.
You've had sex once. How was it?
I still matter.
Okay,ted,go win the bet.
You have my bles ng.
Sishe's a wonderful girl.
I should know.
Oh,okay.
Okay,I see what you're doing.
We've never shared a woman,have
we,ted? Isn't that funny?
You're with her now.
I was with her a year ago.
You figure,for her,that's
like 200 showers ago.
You've got to ask
yourself,ted,is 200 enough?
You know what?
I don't mind.
No,of course you don't mind.
Just like the second guy to climb mount everest
didn't mind getting all the way to the top
only to find sir edmund hillary's
flagpole thrust into its supple peak.
No,I'm sure when you're with her,I'll
be the furthest thing from your mind.
Kissing what I've already kissed,
nuzzling what I've
already nuzzled,going...
on what I've already gone on.
- Barney,I'm not afraid of catching your cooties,'kay?
- Really?
- Ted's not afraid of cooties?
- No.
Okay,well,then I guess you'd have no
problem having a sip of my gin and tonic.
Fine.
and I only stirred that with my pinky.
Guess who loves robin.
Kids. Kids love robin.
Doug thinks I'm pretty cool.
Really,that's great!
You and george,all thanks to me.
Yeah,I'm going to have
to break up with him.
What?
Well,it's just...
it's getting a little
bittoo serious with the kid.
Just not what I'm looking for.
So better I break it off now
before he gets too attached.
What?
I hate to tell you,but... too late.
MY NEW MOMMY He
drew it in class today.
Oh,crap.
there's no way that's a picture of me.
That woman has on hoop earrings.
I don't even own hoop earrings.
I have one pair and they're
gold. Those are fruit loops.
You are so in denial right now and you're
doing what you always do in relationships:
The second you get close
to a guy,you want to bail.
Okay,granted,he's si
but the point stands.
Well,we'll ask the guys.
They'll tell you that's not me.
That's totally you.
Wh... you guys are crazy.
Hey,who drew the picture of robin?
It's not me.
You're joking,right?
It's not me!
My new mommy.
Kind of has a nice ring to it.
Hey,now that you're a mom,are you going to start wearing
those totally awesome jeans that go right up to your boobs?
Do you guys really think this is me?
Honey,it's you.
And if you're going to break up with
george,you have to break up with his kid,too.
Really?
Yeah,you can't just abandon him.
You have to talk to him.
Roanscome on,robin,you know
it's the right thing to do.
Oh,man.
Doug was right: You
are a pain in the ass.
So I had a really nice time tonight.
- Me,too.
- Yeah?
Hey,ted,pucker up all you
want,but I was here first.
From this spot,
I also launched an expedition to
those two large ridges down there.
ted?
Something wrong?
Hey,doug.
Are you here to see my dad?
He's taking a shower.
Actually,I came to see you.
I wrote a poem. Do you want to hear it?
Sure. Why not?
To my new mommy.
You are pretty.
You are nice.
And you smell like daisies.
Aw,that is so sweet.
Even though it doesn't rhyme.
Look,uh,doug.
There's no good way to say this,uh...
aunt robin didn't know what to say.
This kid has never been dumped before.
But then she realized...
this kid had never been dumped before.
She could use every clich? in the book.
We need to talk.
I just think,um,we both could
use some space right now.
It's not you. It's me.
I know this hurts,but you
deserve someone better.
I'm just really trying to
focus on my career right now.
You know?
I just hope we can still be friends.
I'm brooke. I'm here
for my date with george.
You must be the babysitter.
I had so much coffee earlier. I need
to run to the loo,but hey,dougie.
What the hell was that?
That was my new mom.
So...
this picture is not of me?
Why would I draw a picture of you?
How many dates has she
been on with your dad?
Two.
I've been on,like,five
and you like her better?
We just really connected.
And what about me?
You think I just go around pouring
cereal for every boy in town?
Why are you getting so upset,roberta?
Robin. My name is robin.
Like the bird,remember?
Whatever.
So that's it,huh?
- Look,you're great,but...
- yeah.
There's always a but.
Well,I couldn't do it.
I broke up with her.
Thanks a lot,by the way.
A beautiful,sexy girl and all I could
think about was you being there first.
You were stuck in my head
like a chumbawamba song.
Which chumbawamba song?
Well,what an interesting turn of events.
It looks like I'm going to win.
What do you mean win? You
couldn't even talk to her.
You tried and you got slapped.
That's what you think happened.
Okay,great,rule #1: No eye
patches or props of any...
here's the deal: My friend just
got dumped,so he's a little shy,
but he'd love to buy you a
drink and get to know you.
The problem is,he thinks a pretty girl
like you won't go for a guy like him.
So would you slap me across the face so he can
see you're not into guys who'd feed you lines?
What do you say? For my friend?
You are so sweet.
So now,whatever nice things
ted does for her,in her mind,
I'm the guy who's even nicer than him.
So you never slept with her?
Not even at all.
Wow,that's good.
It gets better.
Remember ted's phone conversation?
Well,have fun in yoga.
Well...
- I am...
- sorry.
- Stacey,right?
- Yeah...
- oh,you're ted's friend from the bar,right?
- Yeah.
- Wait,don't tell me you go to yoga here,too.
- I do.
She plays bass in a reggae band.
And then I'm going to head
out to a reggae concert.
- I'm a huge fan of reggae.
- Oh,my gosh!
- I play in a reggae band.
- No way.
I wonder why ted didn't tell me about
that. Like I said,I'm a huge reggae fan.
Well...
I should go inside.
After a while,crocodile.
- See you later,allig...
- see you later,allig...
we are two peas.
wow,well,take care.
Um,namaste.
You are a sociopath.
And that was my yoga mat.
so now with ted out of the picture,
I'm going to swoop in
and win the whole thing.
Why? Parce que j'ai le jeu,mes chiennes.
Translation: 'Cause I got game,bitches.
No. No,this doesn't
prove anything because...
hold on a second.
It's stacey.
Hey,stace?
What happened?
He did not!
Stay there.
I'll be right over.
I should've just worn
that stupid eye patch.
Oh,I can't believe you got
dumped by a six-year-old.
Whatever. He's a stupid-head.
I'm just... I'm done with kids.
Of course,robin eventually
made her peace with kids.
And as you guys know,she went on to appear
in some very important works of art: Yours.
US AND AUNT ROBIN
US AND AUNT ROBIN AT THE ZOO
US AND AUNT ROBIN AT THE BEACH
one month later
hey.
You know,I really appreciate how cool
you've been about us taking things slow.
since ted,you know,I...
I don't really want to
get physical too fast.
That's what makes you so special,baby.
Anyway,I am so psyched to be
playing sunsplash tomorrow.
We go on sometime
between 11:00 and 6:00,
so you probably want to get
there before 9:00 just to be safe.
Oh,and it's gonna be muddy.
翻译: SharonTang 雨池